

Beata Greń-Onderko beongren@gmail.com (+44) 7448 245462 d.o.b.: 31st August 1963 Polish full driving license CRB on demand

Beata Greń-Onderko

Shop assistant

Career Profile I am a committed, hard working person who wants to make use of her abilities to listen to people, understand their needs, patiently take care and respect them. I have livelong experience in childcare (in Poland, France and UK) but I am willing to learn and participate in professional training for health care assistant, as I have experience in this kind of care.

Key experience I regularly cook meal for an older lady, and sometimes help with health care. These meals are always made with very fresh ingredients. She particularly likes the soups that I make. I have also cooked for my large family for 25 years, including many times with gatherings of over 20 people. I can offer the following skills and personal qualities:

- hands-on experience of preparing food for large number of people
- good understanding of foods and nutrition suited to older people and basic hygiene good practice
- good knowledge of vegetarian dishes
- a good team worker
- a caring attitude to older people
- reliability and punctuality
- an awarness of costs in food preparation and interest in cuisine from different countries
- a willigness to learn and undertake an further training necessary to do a good job.
- an ability to learn quickly

Work experience

17th May 2016 - ...

Sales assistant in Euro Garages (Ross-On-Wye) FULL TIME

8th May 2016 - ...

Cleaner (PART TIME) at Parkfields Country House. Duties: keeping all areas of Parkfields Country house clean and tidy, sorting laundry, dusting, polishing, sweeping.

September 2015-April 2016

Au pair for two children : girl 22 months, girl 4.5 years old in Ross-on-Wye, UK

October 1986-June 1987

Afternoon babysitting in family orphanage: girl(8 years old); boy (8 years old); girl aged 12 with schizophrenia;

1988-89

24h/7 babysitting of 9-month old baby girl;

July 1990-August 1991

Au pair in Ventabren, France; 2 children: boy aged 1,5 and boy aged 3 as well as taking care of the house (cleaning, cooking, laundry etc.)

Training and Courses

03rd October 1985 -19th May 1986

First aid course at Polish Red Cross at PRC Wrocław

August 1986

One month <u>language scholarship</u> founded by French Embassy at University of Grenoble, France

02nd March 2009-30th June 2009

Training in Social Integration Center (Centrum Integracji Społecznej) in Wrocław. Aim: schooling in licensing and running social cooperative (446 hours)

10th September 2009-19th December 2009

English language course at Pre-Intermediate level in Yellow Language Center Sp. z.o.o (64 hours)

January - August 2010

Participation in "Women professionally active- It's me" project concerning: 60h of <u>UE projects management</u> training, 8h of <u>labour legislation</u> training, 30h of <u>computer skills</u> training (MS Office), 8h of <u>labour market</u> training, 8h of <u>psychology</u> workshop, 8h <u>auto presentation</u> skills training, english language course finished with TOEIC exam

2009-2011

French language course at level B2/C1 in Alliance Français Language School in Wrocław (3 semesters)

October 2014-July 2015

English language course at A2 level (coursebook A2/B1) with final exam

Education

1982-1987

Studies at Faculty of National Economics at Oskar Lange's Academy of Economics (now University of Economics) in Wrocław

Skills and Interests

Languages

English A2
French B2
German A1

Interests

- \circ Natural medicine \circ Sports: fitness and \circ Films and festivals and herbalism skiing
- Gardening Classical music

References

References upon request.